<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="BLE_Audio_Control">BLE Audio Control</string>
    <string name="Firmware_upgrade">Firmware upgrade</string>
    <string name="Idle">Idle</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description">Navigate home</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description_format">%1$s, %2$s</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_subtitle_description_format">%1$s, %2$s, %3$s</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_up_description">Navigate up</string>
    <string name="abc_action_menu_overflow_description">More options</string>
    <string name="abc_action_mode_done">Done</string>
    <string name="abc_activity_chooser_view_see_all">See all</string>
    <string name="abc_activitychooserview_choose_application">Choose an app</string>
    <string name="abc_search_hint">Search…</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_clear">Clear query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_query">Search query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_search">Search</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_submit">Submit query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_voice">Voice search</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with">Share with</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with_application">Share with %s</string>
    <string name="abc_toolbar_collapse_description">Collapse</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="access_point_mode_found">SensorTag WiFi in Access Point mode Found !</string>
    <string name="access_point_mode_found_message">is in Access Point mode, would you like to provision this device as a station in another wLAN ?</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="adp_ch_mask_high_default">00FF00FF00FF00FF00</string>
    <string name="adp_ch_mask_high_label">CH 64 - 131</string>
    <string name="adp_ch_mask_low_default">00FF00FF00FF00FF</string>
    <string name="adp_ch_mask_low_label">CH 0 - 63</string>
    <string name="adp_current_network_mask_label">Current network channel mask:</string>
    <string name="adp_current_pan_id_label">Current PAN ID:</string>
    <string name="adp_current_pan_id_text">0xXXXX</string>
    <string name="adp_provisioning_state_text">UNPROVISIONED</string>
    <string name="adp_set_network_channel_mask_button_text">Set network channel mask</string>
    <string name="adp_set_pan_id_button_text">Set PAN ID</string>
    <string name="adp_start_provisioning_button_text">Start provisioning (Connect)</string>
    <string name="adp_title">Current provisioning state:</string>
    <string name="advanced">Advanced</string>
    <string name="afnisstwo_off_chip_header">OFF-CHIP OAD IMAGES</string>
    <string name="afnisstwo_on_chip_header">ON-CHIP OAD IMAGES</string>
    <string name="ambient_temperature">Ambient Temperature</string>
    <string name="apache_license_2_0">Apache License Version 2.0, January 2004 http://www.apache.org/licenses/ TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION 1. Definitions. \"License\" shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction, and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document. \"Licensor\" shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by the copyright owner that is granting the License. \"Legal Entity\" shall mean the union of the acting entity and all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition, \"control\" means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity. \"You\" (or \"Your\") shall mean an individual or Legal Entity exercising permissions granted by this License. \"Source\" form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications, including but not limited to software source code, documentation source, and configuration files. \"Object\" form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical transformation or translation of a Source form, including but not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation, and conversions to other media types. \"Work\" shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work (an example is provided in the Appendix below). \"Derivative Works\" shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of, the Work and Derivative Works thereof. \"Contribution\" shall mean any work of authorship, including the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, \"submitted\" means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems, and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise designated in writing by the copyright owner as \"Not a Contribution.\" \"Contributor\" shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and subsequently incorporated within the Work. 2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of, publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form. 3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable (except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made, use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work, where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s) with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You institute patent litigation against any entity (including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate as of the date such litigation is filed. 4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You meet the following conditions: (a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or Derivative Works a copy of this License; and (b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices stating that You changed the files; and © You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and attribution notices from the Source form of the Work, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works; and (d) If the Work includes a \"NOTICE\" text file as part of its distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or, within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed as modifying the License. You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and may provide additional or different license terms and conditions for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use, reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with the conditions stated in this License. 5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise, any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of this License, without any additional terms or conditions. Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed with Licensor regarding such Contributions. 6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor, except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file. 7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each Contributor provides its Contributions) on an \"AS IS\" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License. 8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory, whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise, unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill, work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor has been advised of the possibility of such damages. 9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer, and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity, or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability. END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS APPENDIX: How to apply the Apache License to your work. To apply the Apache License to your work, attach the following boilerplate notice, with the fields enclosed by brackets \"[]\" replaced with your own identifying information. (Don\'t include the brackets!) The text should be enclosed in the appropriate comment syntax for the file format. We also recommend that a file or class name and description of purpose be included on the same \"printed page\" as the copyright notice for easier identification within third-party archives. Copyright [yyyy] [name of copyright owner] Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0 Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="app_closing">Bluetooth off, app now closing</string>
    <string name="app_name">SimpleLink Starter</string>
    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">android.support.design.widget.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="application_License">Application License</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_factory_default">Are you sure you would like to return SensorTag firmware to factory default?</string>
    <string name="auth_google_play_services_client_facebook_display_name">Facebook</string>
    <string name="auth_google_play_services_client_google_display_name">Google</string>
    <string name="balanced">Balanced</string>
    <string name="barometer">Barometer</string>
    <string name="battery_saver">battery saver</string>
    <string name="battery_saver_dialog_message">In \"Battery Saver\" mode the SensorTag device shuts down after approximately 120 seconds of inactivity.\10\10Are you sure you would like to put your SensorTag device in \"Battery Saver\" mode?\10\10 - Note that setting the ST device to this mode can only be effective after the ST device had been provisioned.</string>
    <string name="battery_saver_dialog_title">Battery Saver Mode</string>
    <string name="block">Block :</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_error_text">Bluetooth error/Bluetooth not turned on - Please verify Bluetooth availability</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_smart_devices">BLUETOOTH LOW ENERGY DEVICES</string>
    <string name="bs">----B/s</string>
    <string name="bt_device_show_options_sensor_view">Sensor View</string>
    <string name="btn_txt_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="bytes">Bytes :</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="characteristic_title">Characteristic Title</string>
    <string name="clear_recordings">Clear recordings</string>
    <string name="cloud_config_dialog_broker_port">Broker Port :</string>
    <string name="cloud_config_dialog_clean_session_checkbox_title">Clean session</string>
    <string name="cloud_config_dialog_cloud_broker_address">Broker Address :</string>
    <string name="cloud_config_dialog_cloud_service">Cloud service :</string>
    <string name="cloud_config_dialog_device_id">Device id:</string>
    <string name="cloud_config_dialog_password">Password :</string>
    <string name="cloud_config_dialog_publish_topic">Publish Topic :</string>
    <string name="cloud_config_dialog_save_button_text">Save settings</string>
    <string name="cloud_config_dialog_title">Cloud Configuration</string>
    <string name="cloud_config_dialog_use_ssl_checkbox_title">Use SSL</string>
    <string name="cloud_config_dialog_username">Username :</string>
    <string name="cloud_url">Cloud URL</string>
    <string name="cloud_url_with_colon">Cloud URL :</string>
    <string name="color_picker">Color Picker</string>
    <string name="common_android_wear_notification_needs_update_text">%1$s requires an update to the Android Wear app.</string>
    <string name="common_android_wear_update_text">%1$s won\'t run unless you update the Android Wear app.</string>
    <string name="common_android_wear_update_title">Update Android Wear</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_api_unavailable_text">%1$s requires one or more Google Play services that are not currently available. Please contact the developer for assistance.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_button">Enable Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_text">%1$s won\'t work unless you enable Google Play services.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_title">Enable Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_error_notification_requested_by_msg">Requested by %1$s</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_button">Get Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_text_phone">%1$s won\'t run without Google Play services, which are missing from your phone.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_text_tablet">%1$s won\'t run without Google Play services, which are missing from your tablet.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_title">Get Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_invalid_account_text">The specified account does not exist on this device. Please choose a different account.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_invalid_account_title">Invalid Account</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_needs_enabling_title">An application requires Google Play services to be enabled.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_network_error_text">A data connection is required to connect to Google Play services.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_network_error_title">Network Error</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_notification_needs_update_title">An application requires an update for Google Play services.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_notification_ticker">Google Play services error</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_sign_in_failed_text">Error signing in the specified account. Please choose a different account.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_sign_in_failed_title">Sign in failed</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unknown_issue">Unknown issue with Google Play services.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unsupported_text">%1$s relies on Google Play services, which is not supported by your device. Contact the manufacturer for assistance.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unsupported_title">Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_button">Update</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_text">%1$s won\'t run unless you update Google Play services.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_title">Update Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_updating_text">%1$s won\'t run without Google Play services, which are currently updating.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_updating_title">Google Play services are updating</string>
    <string name="common_open_on_phone">Open on phone</string>
    <string name="con_interval">Con. Interval :</string>
    <string name="configure_a_new_wifi_device">Configure a new WiFi device</string>
    <string name="configure_new_wifi_device">Configure a new WiFi device</string>
    <string name="connect_to_st_after_reboot">Connect to ST after reboot</string>
    <string name="connected_to_sensortag_ap">Connected to SensorTag AP</string>
    <string name="connection_control_service">Connection Control Service</string>
    <string name="connection_failed_message">Failed to connect to SensorTag device, Please make sure your SensorTag device is ready for firmware upgrade, and restart the firmware upgrade process.</string>
    <string name="connection_failed_title">Connection Failed</string>
    <string name="connection_status">Connection status :</string>
    <string name="cur_image">Device image:</string>
    <string name="current_android_connection_priority">Current Android connection priority :</string>
    <string name="current_connection_interval">Current connection interval :</string>
    <string name="current_firmware">Current Firmware</string>
    <string name="current_fw">Current Firmware :</string>
    <string name="current_slave_latency">Current Slave Latency :</string>
    <string name="current_supervision_timeout">Current Supervision Timeout :</string>
    <string name="device_information_service">Device Information Service</string>
    <string name="discovering_services">Discovering Services</string>
    <string name="display_text">Display Text :</string>
    <string name="dmm_rd_toggle_conc_led_button">Toggle Collector LED</string>
    <string name="do_not_show_again">Do not show again</string>
    <string name="double_zero_units">0.0 Units</string>
    <string name="eight">8.0</string>
    <string name="eighty">80:00:00:00:00:00</string>
    <string name="ellipsis">. . . .</string>
    <string name="enable_clock">Enable Clock</string>
    <string name="eoad_block_size_title">Block Size:</string>
    <string name="eoad_current_block_label_title">Current Block:</string>
    <string name="eoad_current_bytes_title">Current Bytes:</string>
    <string name="eoad_custom_file_button_select_file">Select Custom FW</string>
    <string name="eoad_dialog_title">Enhanced OAD</string>
    <string name="eoad_mtu_size_title">MTU Size:</string>
    <string name="eoad_select_chip_type_title">Chip Type:</string>
    <string name="eoad_select_file_button_preparing">Preparing ...</string>
    <string name="eoad_select_file_button_select_file">Select Factory FW</string>
    <string name="eoad_status_label_title">Status:</string>
    <string name="eoad_total_block_label_title">Total Blocks:</string>
    <string name="eoad_total_bytes_title">Total Bytes:</string>
    <string name="factory_default">factory default</string>
    <string name="feb">0.91 (Feb 13 2015)</string>
    <string name="fff_description_label">This 15.4 device is SM enabled. Please select an authentication mode below</string>
    <string name="fff_sm_title">TI 15.4 Security Manager</string>
    <string name="fff_status_text">Status: N/A</string>
    <string name="fffsm_spinner_prompt">Auth mode selection</string>
    <string name="file_open_failed">File open failed:</string>
    <string name="firmware">Firmware :</string>
    <string name="firmware_rev">Firmware Rev:</string>
    <string name="firmware_revision">Firmware Revision:</string>
    <string name="firmware_upgrade">Firmware Upgrade</string>
    <string name="five_hundred">500</string>
    <string name="five_out_of_five">-----/-----</string>
    <string name="four_out_of_four">----/----</string>
    <string name="fp_prov_title">TI DMM Provisioning Interface</string>
    <string name="fw_entry_table_row_Title">Title</string>
    <string name="fw_entry_table_row_subtitle">Sub Title</string>
    <string name="general_info">This application connects to Bluetooth® and WiFi devices from Texas Instruments Inc.\10\10Supported Android OS versions are from 5.0 and upwards.\10\10</string>
    <string name="hardware_rev">Hardware Rev:</string>
    <string name="hardware_revision">Hardware Revision:</string>
    <string name="high">High</string>
    <string name="humidity">Humidity</string>
    <string name="hundred_ms">100ms</string>
    <string name="idle">idle</string>
    <string name="image">Image</string>
    <string name="interrogating_device">Interrogating device</string>
    <string name="invert_display">Invert Display</string>
    <string name="ip_address">IP Address :</string>
    <string name="ir_temperature">IR Temperature</string>
    <string name="jmdns_project_license">JmDNS project license :</string>
    <string name="keys">Keys</string>
    <string name="lamp_control">Lamp Control</string>
    <string name="license_agreement">License Agreement</string>
    <string name="light">Light</string>
    <string name="load_image_a">Image A</string>
    <string name="load_image_b">Image B</string>
    <string name="load_image_c">Custom</string>
    <string name="low_pwr">Low Pwr</string>
    <string name="mac_address">MAC Address :</string>
    <string name="manufacturer_name">Manufacturer Name:</string>
    <string name="minus_sign">-</string>
    <string name="mobile_data">Mobile\10Data</string>
    <string name="model_NR">Model NR:</string>
    <string name="model_nr">Model Nr:</string>
    <string name="movement">Movement</string>
    <string name="ms">-- ms</string>
    <string name="na">N/A</string>
    <string name="network_ssid">Network SSID:</string>
    <string name="new_device_instructions">Pull out the clear battery tab\10Wait until the red LED blinks 3 times\10Wait for list of found devices to appear</string>
    <string name="new_image">Update image:</string>
    <string name="newest_firmware">Newest Firmware</string>
    <string name="no">NO</string>
    <string name="no_image">Not an OAD image</string>
    <string name="no_image_sel">No image selected</string>
    <string name="not_compatible">Not compatible</string>
    <string name="not_connected">Not connected</string>
    <string name="oad_dialog_old_fw_0_89_cc26xx">Firmware version 0.89 detected, to upgrade to latest firmware we will need to upgrade in two stages, first stage to v0.91 and second stage to v1.01</string>
    <string name="oad_dialog_programming_finished">Firmware upgrade finished, the device should now disconnect, this will be evident by the device restarting and LED start blinking again. r\10r\10If this should not happen, upgrade failed, you should try to upgrade again.</string>
    <string name="oad_dialog_progress">0.0%</string>
    <string name="oad_dialog_title">OAD Programming</string>
    <string name="oad_file_select_button">Browse</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="open_in_web_browser">Open in Web Browser</string>
    <string name="ota_failed_dialog_message">SensorTag device firmware upgrade process had failed.\10\10Would you like to try again?</string>
    <string name="ota_failed_dialog_title">Firmware Upgrade Process Failed</string>
    <string name="ota_failed_progress_dialog_message_1">SensorTag firmware upgrade process preparing to restart</string>
    <string name="ota_failed_progress_dialog_message_2">Committing Factory Default</string>
    <string name="ota_failed_progress_dialog_message_3">Reconnecting to SensorTag device for factory default</string>
    <string name="ota_failed_progress_dialog_message_4">Reconnecting to SensorTag device after factory default</string>
    <string name="ota_failed_progress_dialog_message_5">Restarting firmware upgrade process</string>
    <string name="ota_failed_progress_dialog_title">Restarting Firmware Upgrade Process</string>
    <string name="out_of_date_firmware_found">SensorTag WiFi with out-of-date firmware found !</string>
    <string name="out_of_date_firmware_found_message">has out-of-date firmware, would you like to upgrade it to the latest firmware ?</string>
    <string name="out_of_date_firmware_title">Out-of-Date Firmware</string>
    <string name="packets_per_timer_notif">Packets per timer/notif</string>
    <string name="please_tap_again_to_exit">Please tap again to exit</string>
    <string name="plus_sign">+</string>
    <string name="preferences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="prefs">Preferences</string>
    <string name="prerequisites">Prerequisites</string>
    <string name="prerequisites_message">While using this application,\10please make sure that either the automatic switch to mobile data when internet is unavailable via WiFi setting is disabled (should be in Wi-Fi settings or Advanced Wi-Fi settings), or disable mobile data usage completely.</string>
    <string name="prog_ogoing">NB! Not permitted to close this view during OAD transfer</string>
    <string name="programming_image">Programming image :</string>
    <string name="progress">Progress</string>
    <string name="progress_info">Discovered x of x services</string>
    <string name="progress_title">Discovering Services</string>
    <string name="provisioning">Provisioning</string>
    <string name="provisioning_finished">Provisioning Finished :</string>
    <string name="provisioning_ready">Provisioning ready</string>
    <string name="prz_led_service_name">LED Service</string>
    <string name="push_to_cloud">Push to Cloud </string>
    <string name="recorded_audio_files">Recorded audio files</string>
    <string name="return_to_factory_default">Return to Factory Default</string>
    <string name="returning_to_factory_default">Returning to factory default</string>
    <string name="returning_to_factory_default_message">SensorTag device returning to factory default firmware version</string>
    <string name="rx_data">RX Data</string>
    <string name="rx_request">RX Request</string>
    <string name="scan_timeout_dialog_message">No SensorTag WiFi devices to configure were discovered at this time.\10\10Please make sure your SensorTag device is turned on and ready to be configured, and try again.</string>
    <string name="scan_timeout_dialog_title">No SensorTag WiFi devices were discovered</string>
    <string name="security_key">Security Key:</string>
    <string name="security_type">Security type:</string>
    <string name="select_fw_file">Select FW file</string>
    <string name="selected">selected</string>
    <string name="sensor_period">Sensor period :</string>
    <string name="sensor_state">Sensor State :</string>
    <string name="sensor_tag">SensorTag</string>
    <string name="sensortag">SensorTag(SensorTag)</string>
    <string name="sensortag_v3.0">SensorTag v3.0</string>
    <string name="serial_NR">Serial NR:</string>
    <string name="serial_nr">Serial Nr:</string>
    <string name="set_android_connection_priority">Set Android connection priority :</string>
    <string name="set_color">Set Color</string>
    <string name="set_connection_interval">Set Connection interval</string>
    <string name="seven_point_five" />
    <string name="sevenpointfive">7.5</string>
    <string name="software_rev">Software Rev:</string>
    <string name="software_revision">Software Revision:</string>
    <string name="speed">Speed :</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="start_firmware_upgrade">Start Firmware upgrade</string>
    <string name="start_prog">Start Programming</string>
    <string name="starting_service">Starting Service …</string>
    <string name="status">Status :</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">999+</string>
    <string name="stay_awake">stay\10awake</string>
    <string name="stay_awake_dialog_message">In \"Stay Awake\" mode the SensorTag device does not automatically shut down after an inactivity period, and thus drains battery quickly.\10\10Are you sure you would like to put your SensorTag device in \"Stay Awake\" mode?\10\10 - Note that setting the ST device to this mode can only be effective after the ST device had been provisioned.</string>
    <string name="stay_awake_dialog_title">Stay Awake Mode</string>
    <string name="stock_images">Stock Images</string>
    <string name="system_id">System ID:</string>
    <string name="table_row_generic_table_row">Generic Characteristic</string>
    <string name="the_eclipse_paho_project_license">The Eclipse Paho project license :</string>
    <string name="third_party_component_licenses">Third party component licenses</string>
    <string name="thousand">1000</string>
    <string name="thousand_ms">1000ms</string>
    <string name="throughputtest_tablerow_PDU_length">Set PDU Length :</string>
    <string name="throughputtest_tablerow_bytes_per_second">Bps</string>
    <string name="throughputtest_tablerow_current_speed">Current Speed :</string>
    <string name="throughputtest_tablerow_phy_coded_mode_switch">Coded</string>
    <string name="throughputtest_tablerow_phy_name">Current PHY</string>
    <string name="throughputtest_tablerow_phy_name_def">Unknown</string>
    <string name="throughputtest_tablerow_phy_one_mbps_mode_switch">1 Mbps</string>
    <string name="throughputtest_tablerow_phy_selection">Set current PHY used :</string>
    <string name="throughputtest_tablerow_phy_two_mbps_mode_switch">2 Mbps</string>
    <string name="throughputtest_tablerow_throughput_test_enable">Enable Throughput Test</string>
    <string name="throughputtest_tablerow_title">Throughput Test Service</string>
    <string name="ti_dmm_zigbee_switch_battery_level">--%</string>
    <string name="ti_logo">TI Logo</string>
    <string name="timer_delay">Timer Delay :</string>
    <string name="title_oad">Firmware Update (OAD)</string>
    <string name="tr_dmm_zigbee_target_endpoint">Not Read</string>
    <string name="tr_zigbee_target_address">Not Read</string>
    <string name="tr_zigbee_target_address_type">Not Read</string>
    <string name="triple_zero_units">0.00 Units</string>
    <string name="ttptr_current_packets_per_second">Current Packet Rate:</string>
    <string name="twenty_five_hundred_ms">2500ms</string>
    <string name="tx_data">TX Data</string>
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="unknown_date">X.XX (Unknown date)</string>
    <string name="use_notifications">Use notifications :</string>
    <string name="version">Version :</string>
    <string name="volume_meter">Volume Meter</string>
    <string name="waiting_for_st_device_to_reboot">Waiting for ST device to reboot</string>
    <string name="waiting_for_st_device_to_reboot_message">After reboot is complete, please choose ST device from devices list</string>
    <string name="wake_on_shake">Wake On Shake </string>
    <string name="wifi_devices">WIFI DEVICES</string>
    <string name="wifi_settings">Wifi\10Settings</string>
    <string name="xx">xx</string>
    <string name="xx_ms">xx ms</string>
    <string name="years_texas_instruments">2013–2018 Texas Instruments Inc.</string>
    <string name="yes">YES</string>
    <string name="zero">0</string>
    <string name="zero_ms">0 ms</string>
    <string name="zero_percent">0.0%</string>
    <string name="zero_point_nine_nine_one">0.991</string>
</resources>
